- Up in the sky, look.
-It's a bird.
- It's a plane.
- It's Superman.
In the endless reaches of the universe...
...there once existed a planet
known as Krypton.
A planet that burned like a green star
in the distant heavens.
There, civilization was far advanced,
and it brought forth a race of supermen...
...whose mental and physical powers...
...were developed
to the peak of human perfection.
But there came a day when giant quakes
threatened to destroy Krypton forever.
One of the planets' leading scientists,
sensing the approach of doom...
...placed his infant son in a rocket ship
and sent it in the direction of the Earth...
...just as Krypton exploded.
The rocket ship sped
through star-studded space...
...landing safely on Earth
with its precious burden...
...Krypton's sole survivor.
A passing motorist found the uninjured
child and took it to an orphanage.
As the years went by
and the child grew to maturity...
...he found himself possessed
of amazing physical powers.
Faster than a speeding bullet.
More powerful than a locomotive.
Able to leap tall buildings
at a single bound.
The infant of Krypton is now
the Man of Steel.
Superman.
To best be in a position
to use his amazing powers...
...in a never-ending battle
for truth and justice...
...Superman has assumed
the disguise of Clark Kent...
...mild-mannered reporter
for a great metropolitan newspaper.
Hello, Clark? Are you awake?
I'll say. Who could sleep
through a racket like this?
well, it's been going on every night
since we've been in town.
What do you suppose it could be?
Could be sabotage, I hope.
Me too.
But who?
Clark, do you suppose--?
Yes, Lois?
Nothing.
Just a silly hunch that maybe
Superman might be over here.
Quiet. Do not talk.
This sabotage must stop at once.
Clark. Clark.
It is Superman. I just saw him.
Swell chance they've got of catching him.
- Miss Lane.
- This way, please.
How does it feel to be home?
Smile, please.
How about Clark Kent?
Did he get away?
No. No, he's still over there.
But don't worry,
Superman promised to look after him.
Captioned by Grantman Brown